<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Affirmations</string>
    <string name="affirmation1">When you do something, you should burn yourself up completely, like a good bonfire, leaving no trace of yourself.</string>
    <string name="affirmation2">One must be deeply aware of the impermanence of the world.</string>
    <string name="affirmation3">All true artists, whether they know it or not, create from a place of no-mind, from inner stillness.</string>
    <string name="affirmation4">Have good trust in yourself … not in the One that you think you should be, but in the One that you are.</string>
    <string name="affirmation5">Have the fearless attitude of a hero and the loving heart of a child.</string>
    <string name="affirmation6">Life isn’t as serious as the mind makes it out to be.</string>
    <string name="affirmation7">Let go over a cliff, die completely, and then come back to life — after that you cannot be deceived.</string>
    <string name="affirmation8">Only when you can be extremely pliable and soft can you be extremely hard and strong.</string>
    <string name="affirmation9">Things are as they are. Looking out into the universe at night, we make no comparisons between right and wrong stars, nor between well and badly arranged constellations.</string>
    <string name="affirmation10">If you are unable to find the truth right where you are, where else do you expect to find it?</string>
    <string name="affirmation11">Muddy water is best cleared by leaving it alone.</string>
    <string name="affirmation12">As a bee gathering nectar does not harm or disturb the color and fragrance of the flower; so do the wise move through the world.</string>
    <string name="affirmation13">To accept some idea of truth without experiencing it is like a painting of a cake on paper which you cannot eat.</string>
    <string name="affirmation14">It really boils down to this: that all life is interrelated. We are all caught in an inescapable network of mutuality, tied in a single garment of destiny. Whatever affects one directly, affects all indirectly.</string>
    <string name="affirmation15">For things to reveal themselves to us, we need to be ready to abandon our views about them.</string>
    <string name="affirmation16">Watch what you say, and whatever you say, practice it.</string>
    <string name="affirmation17">Nothing ever exists entirely alone. Everything is in relation to everything else.</string>
    <string name="affirmation18">Zen is not some kind of excitement, but concentration on our usual everyday routine.</string>
</resources>